

# **Quentin Dangles**UX/UI DESIGNER

## PROFILE

Throughout my 7 years working side-by-side with clients, patients and customers, I've developed strong empathy and communication skills.

UX/UI design is a perfect game field to continue applying my professional and soft skills for the betterment of humanity.

# CONTACT

qyu.dangles@gmail.com

+33 6-12-85-44-70

in /quentin-dangles

#### EDUCATION

#### IronHack

UX/UI designer certificate 2019

**Inst. Dauphine d'osteopathie** Osteopathy Diploma 2013

**High School Marie Curie**Scientific Baccalaureate, 2006

# TOOLS&SKILLS

Sketch, Flinto, Photoshop, Trello, Marvel, Invision, Adobe XD.

Trilingual in French, English and Japanese.

# WORK EXPERIENCE

# IronHack, UX/UI designer

MAY 2019 - AUG 2019

(PARIS, FRANCE)

- Provided design solutions to solve user needs and business challenges through User research, Information Architecture, Interaction Design, Visual Design and Prototyping.
- Designed a one-year life cycle website for the Martial Arts festival 2020.
- Built a reliable website based on solid UX research for a lawyer to help her in her fight against human trafficking.
- Have completed several projects, including design of an ecommerce web app, a microsite for curated events and a responsive editorial website.
- UX research articles recorded and highlighted by the UX Collective on Medium.

### Skye Niseko (5-stars Hotel), Duty Manager.

JAN 2019 - MAY 2019.

(HOKKAIDO, JAPAN)

- Handled planning and managed a team of 20 people of different backgrounds and nationalities.
- Raised customer satisfaction by 20% in 6 months.

#### **NES Global School**, Foreign Language instructor

APR 2017 - JAN 2019

(TOKYO, JAPAN)

 Identified students with special requirements and created individualized plans.

#### Louis Vuitton, Assistant manager Headquarter

FEB 2016 - DEC 2016

(PARIS, FRANCE)

- Developed strong communication and organizational skills.
- Worked efficiently under pressure with very demanding visitors.

#### Osteopath

DEC 2013 - DEC 2016

(PARIS, FRANCE)

 Developed strong empathy and human relationship skills.